{
    "subject": "resource/Napoleon_Solo",
    "predicate": "ontology/portrayer",
    "object": "resource/Henry_Cavill",
    "human_readable": "Napoleon Solo was portrayed by Henry Cavill.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9682183265686035,
            "question": "In what kind of media did Henry Cavill portray Napoleon Solo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9098954200744629,
            "question": "Who portrayed Napoleon Solo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.747672438621521,
            "question": "What role did Henry Cavill play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7286143898963928,
            "question": "Is Napoleon Solo a fictional character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7049071788787842,
            "question": "What is the name of the character played by Henry Cavill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.701244592666626,
            "question": "Are there any other actors who have portrayed Napoleon Solo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6391734480857849,
            "question": "What other notable roles has Henry Cavill played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4079657793045044,
            "question": "Is Henry Cavill known for portraying a spy character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.012053069658577442,
            "question": "Can you name a famous spy organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.010317031294107437,
            "question": "What are some popular spy movies or TV shows?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Napoleon Solo was portrayed by Henry Cavill.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8547_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a famous spy organization?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8547_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Henry Cavill known for portraying a spy character?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8547_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other notable roles has Henry Cavill played?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8547_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8547_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8547_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8547_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8547_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8547_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8547_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8547_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8547_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8547_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8547_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly mention that Henry Cavill played the role of Napoleon Solo in \"The Man from U.N.C.L.E.\", thus supporting the statement that Napoleon Solo was portrayed by Henry Cavill."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}